Guide to the John W. Hollister papers,ca. 1980-1990.
Hollister, John W. papers,ca. 1980-1990
- Ultra Violet, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 9)
Looking Left, S.U.N.Y./ Binghamton- 1973 (Single Article- Gay Liberation: A Male Sexist Plot)
Mandate- September 1983.
Matrix: Women's Newsmagazine. Santa Cruz, CA. (2)
Metroline. Feb 29-March 13, 1996. Hartford, CT.
Mix Get Lucky: 13th New York Lesbian & Gay Experimental Film/Video Festival. Nov. 1999. New York, NY.
National Gay and Lesbian Task Force Report- Spring 1993.
The Network: New Jersey's Lesbian/Gay Monthly. June 1992. New Brunswick, NJ.
New Beginnings: for family and friends. Westby, WI. (4)
New directions for Women. Dover, NJ. (2)
Newsline: People with AIDS Coalition of New York. February 1996. New York, NY.
The New York International Festival of Lesbian and Gay Film. May 31-June 17 1990. New York, NY.
New York Native. New York, NY. (3)
Next Magazine. New York, NY. (1)
Nineteen eighty seven Men. Calender: Statics, 1987.
NOW NYC News. Vol. 9 no. 6. New York, NY.
Off our backs: a women's newsjournal. Vol. 20 no. 8. Washington, DC.
Onstott, Kyle. Child of the Sun. Greenwich, CT: Fawcett Publications,1972.
On the Wilde Side: Serving the Tri-State Lesbian & Gay Community. Commack, NY. (4)
Our Stories-Spring/Summer 1991.
Our Voice: About Chemical Dependency and Treatment in the Lesbian/Gay Community. Pride Institute: December 1990.
Outlines- December 1984, February 1985, April 1985, June 1985, September/October 1985, November/December 1985, September/October 1986, April 1986, June/July 1986, November/December 1986, September/October 1986, Summer 1987, December 1987/January 1988, Fall 1988, Winter Eternal (1988), February/March 1989, April/May 1989, Summer 1989, September 1989, November/December 1989, February/March 1990, May 1990, September/October 1990, February/March 1991, September/October 1991, December 1991, June 1992, Summer 1993, Fall 1993, Winter 1993, Spring 1994, Summer 1994, Fall 1994, Winter 1994, Spring 1995, Summer 1995, Winter 1995, April 1996, Winter 1996, Spring 1997, Summer 1997, Spring 1998, Summer 1998, Fall 1998, Winter 1998, Summer 1999.
Out magazine. New York, NY. (3)
Out: Pittsburgh's GLB publication. No. 185. Pittsburgh, PA.
Out in the Mountains: Vermont's Newspaper for Lesbians, Gay Men, and Bisexuals. August 1990. Burlington, VT.
Out Magazine: Washington's Weekly Entertainment Guide. April 29, 1982. Washington, DC.
Outrage- December 1988.
Philadelphia Gay News. Philadelphia, PA. (8)
Physical Culture- April 1926.
The Pink Paper: A News Publication for the Alternative Community of Syracuse. Syracuse, NY. (9)
Playgirl- March 1983.
Positive Living: Publication of the Los Angeles AIDS Project. August 1994. Los Angeles, CA.
POZ. New York, NY. (2)
Pride Guide: The official Guide to Gay/Lesbian Pride Week 84. New York, NY. Tower Press: 1984.
Pride Guide '86. New York, NY. Tower Press: June 1986.
The Public Eye- March 1993.
PWA Coalition Newsline. No. 13. New York, NY.
QW. New York, NY. (8)
Reactions. Issue 89. CA.
Reinhart, Robert C. A History of Shadows. New York: Avon Books, 1982.
RFD. Grinnell, Iowa. (6)
Risky Business. San Francisco, CA: San Francisco AIDS Foundation. 1988.
Rites: for lesbian and gay liberation. Toronto, Canada. (2)
Sanscript- Fall/Winter 1992, Summer 1993, Fall 1994, Spring/Summer 1995.
Sappho's Isle: The Tri-State Lesbian Newspaper. Albertson, NY. (8)
SBC: for the Afrocentric Homosexual Man. Vol. 3, No. 6. Los Angeles, CA.
Seattle Gay News. Vol. 17 no. 30. Seattle, WA.
Second Stone. March/April 1994. New Orleans, LA. (Religious Newspaper)
Sex Essentials- 1993.
Sexual Contact- April 1995, October 1996.
Sexualities News- Summer 2003, Summer 2005.
Short Mountain Goatzette- Summer 1985 and Spring 1986.
Sin Fronteras- Winter 1985.
Society for the Study of Social Problems- Spring 1993, Fall/Winter 1993, Spring/Summer 1994.
Society of Lesbian and Gay Anthropologists- Newsletter- February 1990, October 1990, February 1991, June 1991, October 1991, February 1992, May 1992, October 1992, February 1993, June 1993.
Sociologists’ Lesbian and Gay Caucus Newsletter- Fall 1988, Fall 1989, Spring 1990, Summer 1990, Fall 1990, Winter 1991, Fall 1991/Winter 1992, Spring 1992, Summer 1992, Fall/Winter 1992-1993, Spring 1993, Summer 1993, Fall 1993, Spring 1994, Summer 1994, Fall 1994, 1995, July/August 2001, August 2002.
Sojourner: The Women's Forum. Cambridge, MA. (2)
Southern Voice. Vol. 4, No. 25. Atlanta, GA.
Spank: A Press for the Rest of Us. (Also called Q) Wilkes-Barre, PA. (2)
Stallion- January 1987, July 1987, March 1990.
Stars- September 1983.
Symons, Scott. Helmet of Flesh. New York: Penguin Books USA Inc., 1986.
Task Force Report: Newsletter of the National Gay Task Force. Washington, DC. (4) (I guess this and the next are the same, just name differences)
Task Force Report: Newsletter of the National Gay and Lesbian Task Force. Autumn 1992. Washington, DC.
True Colors: A Newsletter for Counseling Gay and Lesbian Clients. Vol. 1 No. 1, 1993. San Antonio, Texas.
TWN: South Florida's Weekly Gay Alternative. Miami, FL. (1)
UltraViolet: Newsletter of Lesbian and Gay Insurrection. San Francisco, CA. (1)
Utne Reader. March/April 1991. Minneapolis, MN.
Vice. Vol 2, no 2. July 1995. New York, NY.
Volume. Aug 3, 1994. Buffalo, New York.
Warren, Patricia Nell. The Front Runner. New York: Bantam Books, 1975.
The Washington Blade. Washington, DC. (6)
W/E Newsletter. April, 1997. Mattydale, Ny.
Whispering Campaign- magazine, no date.
WNY Community Network's Qnews. Vol. 3, No. 4, April 1997. Buffalo, NY.
Women Source. Vo. 1 no. 3. Pittsburgh, PA.
The Works: Drugs, Sex & AIDS. San Francisco, CA: Impact AIDS. 1987.
Zeta Magazine- January 1987.